Hope runs deep.
The War Below is a war, drama, history film directed by J.P. Watts.
During World War I, a group of British miners are recruited to tunnel underneath no man's land and set bombs
from below the German front in hopes of breaking the deadly stalemate of the Battle of Messines.
William Hawkin, played by Sam Hazeldine.
Hellfire Jack, played by Tom Goodman-Hill.
Harold Stockford, played by Kris Hitchen.
George MacDonald, played by Elliot James Langridge.
Charlie MacDonald, played by Sam Clemmett.
Shorty, played by Joseph Steyne.
The War Below is a 2021 British war film directed by J.P.
Watts, in his directorial debut, and written by Watts and Thomas Woods.
It was released in the United Kingdom on 10 September 2021.
The film is also distributed in Germany, France, Greece,
Australia, the Middle East, South Korea and Japan.
The tone is emotional.